Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series I: Washington Square Dean's Files
  - Subseries D: Administrative Subject Files
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226003 7
    - American Language Institute, 1964-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - American Psychological Association, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - American Research Institute in Turkey, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - American Sociological Society, 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - American Universities Field Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - American University in Cairo, 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Antopol, William, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Apex Project, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Applied Social Research, Center for, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - A etice (Literary Magazine), 1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Area Distribution Requirements, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Army Education Centers 1965 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Arnold Library, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Art Competition, 1961-1965 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Arts and Science Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Arts and Science Research Fund, 1960-1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Arts and Sciences (Magazine), 1961-1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Arts in Higher Education (Carnegie Commission), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Arts, School of the, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Arts, School of the, 1966-1975 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Aspira College Retention Freshman Counseling Program, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Assistant Teacher Program, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1964-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226004 5
    - Association of American Universities, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Astronomy, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Athletics, 1961-1967 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Auditing, 1964-1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Average Computing, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Bachelor of Literature, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Barron's NYU Profile, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bellevue, 1961-1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Benchmark Evaluation Committee, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Jr., Dr. Ivan L., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Berezin, Irving, 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Berg Chair, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Berger, Dean, 1969-1972 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Bernsten, Howard, 1966-1973 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Bicentennial Celebration--US, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Bilingual Education, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Biography, Post Doctoral Seminar, 1963-1966 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Black Experience, Courses on, 1968-1976 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Black Student's Association, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Black Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Black Studies Degree Program, 1969-1972 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Blind Students, 1964-1974 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Blue Key National Honour Fraternity, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Bonus Courses, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Bookman Fund, 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - British Summer Schools, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226005 2
    - Brittany, The, 1969-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Bromberg, Dr. Eleazer, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bulletin, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin Boards, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin Proofs 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin-Type Information for Preregistration Purposes, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bursar, 1964-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Business Manager, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Business Services Coordinator, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Byrnes, Mr. Joseph A., 1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - College, Nature of, and its Deisrable Size, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - College of Business and Public Administration, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Colleges, Private: Five Part Series, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Collegiate Institute, 1acker: Cooperative Arrangements, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Congress on Agriculture in the land of the Bible, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Garage: Proposed, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - General Foods: Fellowships, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Glee Club, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Governmental Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Grace Internships, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Grading: Individual Problems, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Graduate Courses for Undergraduates, 1965-1971 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - GSAS Fellowships, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - GSAS Deanship, 1964-1973 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - GSAS General File, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - GSAS Policies, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration: Newsletter, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Graduate Science School: Proposal, 1966-1974 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Graduate Social Work 1962-, 1962-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226006 0
    - Graduate Work at the Heights, 1965-1967 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Graduates Taking Undergraduate Courses for Credit, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Grants, 1968-1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Great Teacher Awards, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Guidance Associates, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Gulbenkian Fellowships, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Mayerson, Dean Philip: Alumni Association, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Academic Planning: Reports and Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226007 8
    - Commission on Academic Planning: Minutes and Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Task Force on Undergraduate Admissions: Reports and Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Establishment of Banner and Shield, 1965-1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Chancellor Sidney Borowitz: Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - By laws: Reports, 1968-1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Faculty: Arthur M. Crosman, 1966-1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Faculty: Dean Paul Culley, 1966-1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Faculty: Dean David L. Hicks, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Faculty: Kenneth N. McKee, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Faculty: Elsa E. Robinson, 1966-1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Faculty: Sidney Towne, 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Faculty: Anthony Zahareas, 1964-1971 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Prospective Vitae and Remarks, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Institute of Fine Arts, 1958-1969 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Fire Drills, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Flags: For Washington Square College, 1965-1968 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation: Accelerated Masters Program Printed Material, 1963-1974 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Student Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Forensic Festival, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226008 6
    - Fort Bragg: Joint Program, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Founders Day: Printed Material, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Founders Day: Printed Material, 1969-1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - New York University in France: Printed Material, 1961-1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Freshmen: Summary and Reports, 1963-1966 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Freshmen Testing Program, 1961-1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Fulbright: Printed Material, 1965-1974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hall of Fame of New York University, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Harbison Award: Printed Material, 1965-1972 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - John F. Hatchett: Printed Material, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Charles Hayden Foundation for the Life Sciences, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Heights Campus: Proposed Study, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - HEW: Affirmative Action Worksheet, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - James M. Hester: Correspondence Printed Material, 1962-1967 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Hertz, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226009 4
    - Higher Education Opportunity Program: Printed Material, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - High School Students: Special Program, 1964-1966 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming Party: Printed Material, 1971-1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Degree: Nominations, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Honors Studies on Man's Future, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Housing at New York University, 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Meritorious Service Award, 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Public Affairs: Budget Review and Press Office, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - William Von Raab: Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Tenure, 1968-1974 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Calendar: Academic Printed Material, 1968-1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Proposed Change to 4x4, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      bar code #: 3 1142 04226010 2
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Dean Phillip Mayerson Correspondence, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files
  - Committee on Evening Programs, 1963-1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227095 2
  - Evening Students, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Evening Studies, 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Examinations, 1964-1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Expense Cutting New Guidelines, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - External Investigations, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Misc. "F", 1965-1968 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Benefits, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Benefits Office (with retirement plan), 1971-1976 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Career Development, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Interdiscliplinary Faculty Colloquia, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Newsletter, 1970-1979 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1967-1972 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Student Evaulation of Faculty, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Grievance Procedures, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Memo to FAS, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science at Washington Square, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Opportunities, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Personnel Action Procedures, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Release Time, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Relations, 1972-1976 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Union, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Fales Collection/Lectureship, 1963-1968 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - FAS Chairman's Meeting, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Deans Council / Agenda-Correspondence, 1969-1977
  - Federal Funding Outlook for Science, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Federal Register, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Federal Relations Office, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Vice Chancellor for Federal Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Federal Statutes, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Fees, 1963-1975 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Film Conference, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Vice President for Finance - Alan C. Claxton, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Financial Aid Allocation, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Dean of Financial Aid, 1967-1978 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Dean Mayerson Re: Financial Aid Meetings, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Financial Aid Renewal Policy, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - New York University Financial Report, 1972-1977 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Fine Arts, 1968-1975 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Fiscal Review Group Report, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Foreign Students, 1963-1977 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Founders Committee of 100, 1963-1967 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Four Course Plan, 1967-1969 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - NYU in France Contract, 1969-1974 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - NYU in France GBA, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - NYU in France General, 1969-1975 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - NYU in France ICCR, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - NYU in France Winders Trip, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - French, 1969-1975 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - French/Italian, 1968-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227096 0
  - French: Review of Doctoral Program also German, Spanish and Portuguese, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising, 1968-1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Legal Alumni Fundraising R. Martin, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Physics Fundraising, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising Ruder and Finn, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising - Sawhill, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - GSAS Committees, 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - GSAS Curriculum Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - GSAS Faculty Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Associates, 1963-1979 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Geology, 1967-1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - German, 1967/1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Deferred Gifts, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Gifts Statistics, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Goals, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Goals Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Statewide Master Plan - Goals (NYU), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - The Goethe Institute, 1971-1976 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Goldin, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Good Will Ideas, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Governance, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Senate Committee on the Standardization of Grades, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Grade Survey Report, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Grading System, 1962-1969 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Grading System, 1970-1977 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - GSAS General, 1968-1976 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Business Administration, 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Graduate International Study Program, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Grievance Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Heads and Chairmen 1968 to present, 1968-1978 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Health, Eduation and Welfare, 1972-1976 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Health and Health Related Courses, 1971-1979 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Health Services, 1964-1976 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1963-1973 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - High Lights, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - High School Information, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Higher Education Act, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Higher Education Compact (Feasibility Study), 1971 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Higher Education Personnel Training Program, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - History, 1968-975 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - History Graduate, 1969-1975 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Holiday Homecoming Party, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Holiday Homecoming, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Christmas Homecoming Party, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Honors Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Honors and Prizes, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Housing Office General, 1967-1974 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Spring '77 - Humanities Seminar Descriptions, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227097 8
  - IALAC - Ibero-American Language and Area Center, 1969-1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - IALAC Proposals, 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ICSS, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - In-house Candidates, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Doctor Minninberg - Office of Institutional Research, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Institutional Research and Planning, 1967-1975 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1969-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Programs, 1969-1977 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - International Student Center, 1968-1975 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - OE and International Studies, 1969-1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Student Internships, 1976-1981 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Sample Invitations, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - WSC Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Italian, 1968-1975 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Henry James Professorship, 1966-1976 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Japanese Students, 1967-1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Journalism, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Journalism, 1970-1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Journalism Accreditation, 1962-1969 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Journalism Applications for Graduate Study, 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - "News Workshop" - Journalism Dept Newspaper, 1967-1971 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Journalism Fundraising and Gifts, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Journalism Proposal for Graduate Course, 1970-1974 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Junior Science Symposium - U.S. Army Research Office, 1975-1978 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Misc. "K", 1964-1966 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Kenan Professorship, 1966-1971 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Kennedy Foundation, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Kerns Colloquium, 1966-1970 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - The Key Reporter, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Admissions and Tutoring, 1968-1970 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Afro-American Student Center, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Institute of Afro-American Affairs, 1969-1975 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Raymond J. Brienza Director of Financial Aid, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - MLK Jr. Scholarship Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - MLK Jr. Scholarship Program, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Klosk, Stanley H Lecturship, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Misc. "L", 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Laboratory Animal Welfare, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Laboratory Fees, 1963-1967 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Language Laboratory, 1963-1969 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Language Placement, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Lassen Collection, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227098 6
  - School of Law, 1968-1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Legal Counsel - Desai, 1967-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Legal Counsel, 1975-1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Legislation (Goren), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Definition of Liberal Arts, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Liberal Studies B.A., 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Library, 1967-1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Library, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Library, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Library and City, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Library Hours, 1968-1975 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Bobst Library Privileges Information, 1970-1977 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Library Programming, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Lindback Award, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Linguistics, 1968-1975 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - AB/MBA Program, 1970-1976 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - NYU in Madrid, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs - Jane Maggin, 1971-1981 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Mathematics, 1967-1975 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - McKeon, George P., 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Martin Meisel, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Dean Mayerson's Annual Report, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Memorial Resolutions, 1968-1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Leadership Program, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Studies, 1969-1975 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Meyer Physics Building, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Miller, Saul and Bernard, 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - WSUC Model Programs - H. Dworkin, Advisement, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - James Munn, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Music, 1967-1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227099 4
  - Music W/ED, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - NSF Survey, 1967-1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - NYU Today, 1973-1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - NSF Proposals Economy and Sociology, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - NSF, 1974-1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - New York State Direct Assistance Program, 1969-1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - New York State Education Dept, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - New York State Regulations of the Commissioner of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - NYU Introduction by Joseph Heller, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - New York State Visit Re: course practice, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Non-Western Studies Project, 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Norfolk College, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Norfolk Evaluation June 19-20, 1965-1969 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Northeast Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Neareastern, 1966-1975 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Northeast Conference on Higher Education, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Northeastern Region of Academic Affairs Administrators (ACAFAD), 1974 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Dean Noss, 1967-1974 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Nursing Associate Degree, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Nursing Baccalaureate Program, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Nursing Committee, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Nursing Education, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Oliva Commission, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Oliva Proposals, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - O'Mara?, undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Ombudsman, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Open Admission, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Open Space, 1973-1975 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Orientation, 1968-1976 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Michael L. Owen Memorial Prize, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Ottendorfer Memorial Fellowship, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Overhead Charges, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Misc. "P", 1963-1967 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - PBS for Secondary Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04227099 4
  - Parents' Reception, 1967-1973 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Parsons School, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Pass/Fail Option, 1966-1974 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Peace Corps, 1963-1967 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Periodical Clippings Re: Universities, 1969-1974 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Perstare Student Publication, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Petitions, 1964-1975 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Ph.D. Oral Examinations, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1968-1977 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Philosophy, 1968-1975 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Phonathon, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Physics, 1967-1975 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Politics, 1967-1975 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Pollock Dinner, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Photographic Bureau, 1966-1975 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Physical Training, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Physical Science N1, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Placement Careers in Foreign Languages, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Plant and Properties, 1963-1974 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Point Counts - Statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Point Count - From Recorder WSUC, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Planning Board, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)